ISAAC B. CONTEH

PRODUCT DESIGNER & DEVELOPER

0000



ABOUT ME

I'm an enthusiastic and creative Product designer & Frontend Developer with industry experience. I am skilled at taking projects from ideation to development phase. I love widening my horizon and learning new technologies to fast-track my career

EDUCATION

- Dele Peddle High School Sierra Leone (2011-2014)
- Limkokwing University Malaysia (2014-2018)

Bachelor's - Software Engineering with Multimedia CGPA: 3.76

CONTACT/LINKS

- +23280710209
- zacflixx2917@gmail.com
- 6b Standford Drive, Freetown Sierra Leone
- https://isaac-29.netlify.app/
- https://www.behance.net/isaacconteh

SKILLS

- UX Design: Wireframes, User journey maps etc
- UI Design & Prototype: Figma, XD, Sketch, Al ...
- Frontend Development HTML, Css, Js , Flutter ...
- CMS Development- Wordpress, Wix, Shopify ...
- Graphic Design Company graphics / advertisments
- Blogging and Creative content writing

EXPERIENCES

FRONTEND SOFTWARE ENGINEER

GUARANTY TRUST BANK SIERRA LEONE APR 2022 - PRESENT

- Design custermer experience and user interface of company applications using design platforms like Figma and InDesign.
- Develop the frontend code of approved Ui-Ux of company applications using Html,Js, react/React native (Mobile) etc.
- Design basic company brand graphics and corporate advertisements.
- Maintain official website and applications with contents/graphics updates

UI DESIGNER & DEVELOPER

TAMAWAL INC. SAUDI ARABIA JUL 2021 - MAR 2022

- Designing company website pages and mobile application
- Develop the frontend code of approved designsAchievement - Successfully lunched the company's Ltr-Rtl Website and Customer Dashboard (www.tamawal.sa)
- Responsible for the design of company graphics and advertisements

WEB DESIGN INTERN

CSI PROPERTIES - MALAYSIA AUG 2021 - NOV 2021

- Tasked with revamping the official company website built on Wordpress (https://csiprop.com/)
- · Video and Photo editing for official content
- Other basic IT task

FREELANCE PROJECTS

ONLIINE

2020

 Freelance design and development projects.
Project samples can be found in my portfolio or behance sites link from the links section